{
  "users": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "username": "jide",
      "password": "adedeji",
      "logged": "false"
    },
    {
      "username": "mulis",
      "password": "bower",
      "id": 2,
      "logged": "false"
    },
    {
      "username": "a",
      "password": "a",
      "id": 3,
      "logged": "true"
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which Italian film director is considered as the father of the spaghetti western?",
      "option1": "Sergio Leone",
      "option2": "cryff seed",
      "option3": "mason mount",
      "option4": "marcus rashford",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What is the lightest existing metal?",
      "option1": "nickel",
      "option2": "steel",
      "option3": "aluminium",
      "option4": "bronze",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which famous brewer from Amsterdam did die in the year 2002?",
      "option1": "Heineken",
      "option2": "star",
      "option3": "budweiser",
      "option4": "red bull",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What should you do in the Arab countries to show that the food was delicious?",
      "option1": "tofu",
      "option2": "ramen",
      "option3": "Belch",
      "option4": "jelato",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "How many players are on each side of the net in beach volleyball?",
      "option1": "one players",
      "option2": "Two players",
      "option3": "three players",
      "option4": "four players",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "How many times has Michael Schumacher been a Formula 1 champion?",
      "option1": "six times",
      "option2": "five times",
      "option3": "eight times",
      "option4": "Seven times",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Who was the first man to fly around the earth with a spaceship?",
      "option1": "snow",
      "option2": "gagarin",
      "option3": "bosco",
      "option4": "john james",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "On which hemisphere were the most dinosaur skeletons found?",
      "option1": "The northern hemisphere",
      "option2": "The southern hemisphere",
      "option3": "The western hemisphere",
      "option4": "The eastern hemisphere",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What color is cobalt?",
      "option1": "red",
      "option2": "violet",
      "option3": "brown",
      "option4": "blue",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What is the organ that is affected when one is suffering from hepatitis?",
      "option1": "heart",
      "option2": "liver",
      "option3": "pancreas",
      "option4": "bladder",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Which device do we use to look at the stars?",
      "option1": "stethoscope",
      "option2": "guage",
      "option3": "barometer",
      "option4": "Telescope",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Which device was invented by Henry Mill?",
      "option1": "buses",
      "option2": "cars",
      "option3": "computer",
      "option4": "The Typewriter",
      "answer": "4"
    }
  ]
}